{
    "subject": "resource/Emily_Penrose",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bournemouth",
    "human_readable": "Emily Penrose died in Bournemouth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8302222490310669,
            "question": "Where did Emily Penrose die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6863739490509033,
            "question": "What year did Emily Penrose die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5404592752456665,
            "question": "Were there any significant events associated with Emily Penrose's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32841676473617554,
            "question": "What is known about Emily Penrose's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31360962986946106,
            "question": "Were there any notable people who knew Emily Penrose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2833242118358612,
            "question": "What was Emily Penrose's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27372002601623535,
            "question": "Is there any historical context surrounding Emily Penrose's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2130565494298935,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Bournemouth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20094279944896698,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Emily Penrose's family or friends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15973405539989471,
            "question": "Can you find any records or documents related to Emily Penrose?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emily Penrose died in Bournemouth.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4322_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Emily Penrose's family or friends?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4322_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Bournemouth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4322_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any historical context surrounding Emily Penrose's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4322_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4322_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Emily Penrose \"died, unmarried, at 11 Dean Park Road on 26 January 1942\" but also mention she \"moved on the outbreak of war (by which time she was an almost complete invalid) to Bournemouth\". This supports the statement that Emily Penrose died in Bournemouth."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}